ZAYNAB **SALEEM**



SKILLS

- Management
- Communication
- Creative
- Handling visitors
- · Maintaining and managing office Supplies
- · Operating PABX, fax, scanner, photocopying
- Documentation
- MS office Outlook ,PowerPoint and Excel

ACTIVITIES

- Worked as Freelance volunteer for Event of Hum tv channel awards in 2018.
- worked as Freelance event organizer for Nestle Pakistan.

outgoing and highly personable sociology student with almost 4 years experience of Administrative Assistant, Driven to always be prepared to provide help to customers and co-workers. Seeking to broaden my skill set an leverage my Business aptitude.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Office Coordinator (2022)

Currently working as office coordinator at Wild Venture Hotel And Resort

FRONT DESK OFFICER (2021-2022)

Worked as FDO at Tufail Multichem PVT LTD.

 PROTOCOL OFFICER cum. Computer **Operator (2019-2021)**

Worked as Protocol officer Engro Energy Limited

TEACHER 2017-2018

Worked as English and science visiting teacher at The academy

 STUDENT COUNCELOR/ TEACHER (2016)

Worked as Student counselor and English Teacher at The HarracksSchool for 3months

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Arts

UNIVERSITY OF KARACHI

Intermediate

PRE - MEDICAL - Allama Iqbal Govt Degree college

Matriculation

Science - Brooks Grammar School

ACHIEVEMENTS

- worked as certified event organizer for cooperate events(Seminars) For OctaraTCS for 2years
- Certified GDS (Air ticketing) from Shaheen Aviation college in 2016.
- completed Internship for Mass Human Resource servicesin 2013

